- [Instructor] React has a developer tool
that allows the developers
to see the state and the components
and inspect what is going wrong
while building your application.
We'll also install another tool called Postman
so we can test our backend as we build it.
So, let's go ahead and install these tools.
So the first one you need to find is React DevTools,
and if you're using Chrome like me,
what you can do is go directly to the Chrome Web Store
and install that tool.
It should look something like this.
I already have it on my system, so I'm good to go.
But you need to find the React developer tools
and install this,
and this is what it's going to look like.
You're going to have the Components, Profiler,
and if you have Redux,
we're not going to use it in this course,
but if you have Redux in the future,
you can actually also install the Redux tool for your state.
But just for this course,
we're going to have the Components and the Profiler here,
and we'll be able to inspect it
through the React developer tools.
The other tool that I recommend installing as well,
that I use all the time for any of the APIs that I create,
is Postman.
Postman is a great tool to test your APIs
to make any calls for whatever the API you're looking for
with all the information that you need to make the calls,
and then you get the return from the API.
And it's a great tool.
Once you have it installed,
it's going to look something like this.
So as we are installing
and creating our server with the APIs,
we're going to test this right here
and we're going to be able
to get the response from the server
and know that it's working properly.
So take some time, install those tools,
and when you're ready to go for the next video,
I'll see you there.